the junker Queen stands with you
have I seen you before it's possible
life pass through drunk it down once or
twice you're the one who kicked redneck
in the Wicker Basket he started it
I thought a bunch of you bastions once
you all had wheels and big sharp teeth
on second thought that might have been a
dream I had
have you got a hamster in that Mech
um no sure sure I'm watching you
ain't easy is it being in charge of
killers and Mad Men no but I welcome the
challenge we got a lot in common
shame I'm gonna kill you someday indeed
didn't I say I'd rip out your tongue if
I saw you again
my queen your voice ever sonorous is
like a gentle waterfall upon my ears
right after the mission mark my words
didn't I say I'd rip out your tongue if
I saw you again
my queen your voice ever sonorous is
like a gentle waterfall upon my ears
yeah the ears are next
I've met mossies with more brains than
you folks with all due respect my lady I
believe that's a knock against the
junkertown education system
we've got an education system
behave yourself folks I can still have
you executed
so I'm trying to ask everybody this what
is your favorite animal is there a kind
of dingo that is also a shark uh yeah I
can see it
doctor have I really got to eat
vegetables it's like crunch crunch
crunch how long have I got to chew these
Mako the Wreckers want you back thought
you might like to know
they'll hate that I'll pass it along
are you on average more mechanical or
more human
why
trying to figure out whether to scrap
you for parts
hmm
consider the railgun before you decide
I could have run OverWatch much better
than you
and what would you have done differently
I would have caught all the bad guys
then cut their heads off
hmm tempting
there's nothing about you and my files
no images no documents nothing yeah well
on what's the word starts with e
enigmatic that's the one and don't you
forget it
what's the biggest decks you could make
out of hard light
a kilometer tall
but you would not be able to wield it
maybe you wouldn't
how many widows have you made roughly I
do not keep track
well I'm pretty sure I'm ahead
anyone want to hear my favorite joke
about the periodic table not unless you
want that table broken over your head
chip I need you to make me something
else a robot guard dog for me dirt
Garden maybe it can fly you decide
fine
jump I need you to make me something
else a suit of armor right but one that
shouts my name
fine but give me a challenge next time
jump I need you to make me something
else I need a slot bucket that's
bulletproof and don't you dare ask why
fine but give me a challenge next time
Jim I need you to make me something else
a grenade launcher with one trigger
three barrels paint glitter and nails
fine
got any room in that Mac champ I want to
take some souvenirs
you look like a Bruiser wanna be my
bodyguard huh I think you can take care
of yourself
Genji remember the time you tripped over
your sword in training some Ninja it
only happened once once was enough
always wanted one of you in my
collection
quit hiding behind your Shield big girl
I warned you boys
should have listened
Summer Shack Avenged
down you go big man
put a dent in your armor there
hang with rat bags die like rat bags
oh champ you've gone soft
you look better than your fight
shame
would you look at that rat jump Gotta
Kill
good one Mako
show them what's watching
no time for dramatic showdowns we're
scrapping here
ah put your little sword away
I'm not gonna let a vlog in a spooky
mask take me down
oh don't get clever with your queen
all right ladies let's teach these boys
a lesson
both brothers on the same team better
make up before I smash your heads
together
let's see we've got a bot an Angel and
the stupidest man alive does that put us
ahead or behind
looks like somebody wants the death
penalty
your queen thanks ya